<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Sandro Linux</title>
  <description>The Latest News from Oscar Sanderson aka Sandro Linux</description>
  <link>https://www.sandrolinux.com/</link>
  <item>
  <title>Huawei maybe working to build its own semiconductor manufacturing line
  </title>
  <description>Huawei maybe working to build its own semiconductor manufacturing line. This is important since Huawei relys on tsmc to make their Kirin processors but tsmc has said they are going to stop making Kirin chips.</description>
  <link>https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/huaweiworkingtobuilditsownsemiconductorline.html
  </link>
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/applehasbannedfortnite.html
  </link>
  <image>
  https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/FortniteLogo.svg
  </image>
  <title>Fortnite has been banned from the Apple App Store and the Google Play Store
  </title>
  <description>Fortnite has been banned from the Apple App Store and the Google Play Store after Epic games let people bypass the 30% cut Apple and Google imposses on in app purchases
  </description>
  
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/samsungs21notof.html
  </link>
  <title>The next Galaxy s device may not include a time of flight camera
  </title>
  <description>A report from South Korea says the next Samsung s series device will have no time of flight camera
  </description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/telegramisgettinganotableimprovement.html
  </link>
  <title>Telegram is getting a notable improvement
  </title>
  <description>Telegram has announced it will now support Video Calling
  </description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/Facebookappearstobeintegratingthechatsystems.html
  </link>
  <title>Facebook may be integrating the chat systems for Instagram and Messenger
  </title>
  <description>Facebook may be integrating the chat systems for Instagram and Messenger and if you open Instrgram you may get a pop-up saying “There’s a New Way to Message on Instagram”
  </description>
  </item>
    <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/zteunderscreencameraphone
  </link>
  <title>
      ZTE is launching the first phone to have a under display camera The Axon 20 5G
  </title>
  <description>
      ZTE has confirmed that it will be launching The Axon 20 5G the world's first phone with an under-display camera
  </description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/huaweilicenseexpired
  </link>
  <title>
      Huawei devices with google mobile services may no longer get updates
  </title>
  <description>
      The temporary general license that allowed Huawei to conduct limited business with US firms lapsed on August 13. Meaning Huawei devices with Google Services may no longer get updates
  </description>
  </item>
  <item>
  <link>
  https://www.sandrolinux.com/news/carnivalhasrevealedthatitsufferedaransomware.html
  </link>
  <title>
      Carnival has revealed that it suffered a ransomware attack and security breach
  </title>
  <description>
  Carnival has revealed that it suffered a ransomware attack and security breach which occurred last weekend on August the 15th.
  </description>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>
